

# Parag Chavan

Unica Campaign Developer

#### Contact

**Address** 

MUMBAI, India 400086

**Phone** 

7767890068

E-mail

paragchavan10@gmail.com

#### **Skills**

**UNICA** 

ADOBE CAMPAIGN

SQL

CAMPAIGN DEVELOPER

CAMPAIGN MANAGER

**EMAIL MARKETING** 

**ORACLE** 

**CAMPAIGN SPECIALIST** 

With 2.10 years of experience, I excel as a Unica Campaign Developer, proficient in Unica, SQL, and Oracle. My skills encompass campaign development, logic building, SMS, email, and WhatsApp campaign monitoring. I ensure quality via SQL checks. I'm eager to broaden my skills to Adobe and Salesforce tools, aiming to become a dedicated and skilled campaign specialist known for unwavering work ethics.

# **Work History**

2021-11 -Current

## **Unica Campaign Developer**

Customer centria pvt Itd, MUMBAI

To Create campaigns as per Client needs and designing flowcharts from scratch in Unica

Targeting customers and segmenting them accordingly to the requirement using SQL or UNICA.

Perform

Quality analysis (SQL) and peer reviews before launching a campaign to ensure data quality.

Coordinating with Netcore and Karix team to send Email/SMS campaigns

Perform quality analysis (SQL) and peer reviews before launching a campaign to ensure quality data.

Providing Post Deployment Support for any issues.
Responsible for
testing and the quality of data which is to be
delivered

Responsible for testing and the quality of data which is to be delivered

Developed and executed targeted marketing campaigns to promote credit and debit card transactions.

2020-10 -2021-08

# **Business Analyst**

Atidiv pvt Itd, Pune
Served as a liaison between clients and
stakeholders, effectively communicating
data-driven recommendations and insights to drive
business strategies

Analyzed processes, products, services, and systems to identify areas for improvement and optimization through data analysis.

Utilized various analytical tools and techniques to extract meaningful insights from data, facilitating profitable decision-making for the company

## **Education**

2014-07 -2016-07 Master of Computer Applications: Computer Science

Pune University - PUNE